{
    "subject": "resource/Alexander_Holle",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1898-02-27",
    "human_readable": "Alexander Holle was born on February 27, 1898.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9037225246429443,
            "question": "Who was born on February 27, 1898?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8716188669204712,
            "question": "Is February the month of Alexander Holle's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8714814782142639,
            "question": "When was Alexander Holle born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8017142415046692,
            "question": "If someone was born on February 27th, 1898, who are they?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7874177098274231,
            "question": "What year marked Alexander Holle's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517533898353577,
            "question": "What is Alexander Holle's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.637091875076294,
            "question": "February 27th, 1898,  is associated with which individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082015633583069,
            "question": "What is Alexander Holle's birth month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5344837307929993,
            "question": "On what date did Alexander Holle celebrate his first birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47914549708366394,
            "question": "In what year did Alexander Holle come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alexander Holle was born on February 27, 1898.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2417_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what date did Alexander Holle celebrate his first birthday?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2417_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Alexander Holle's birth month?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2417_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=February 27th, 1898,  is associated with which individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2417_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2417_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents contain information that confirms Alexander Holle's birthdate as February 27, 1898."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}